3news.com 2016-06-16

# Privacy Policy | 3News

**Internet Privacy & Cookies Policy **

MG Digital Media Ltd is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This is the website privacy policy for  
www.3news.com (the “Website”). 

This Website Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected on the publicly available sections of the Website, however accessed, and/or used.

We take the privacy of all visitors to this Website very seriously and therefore set out in this privacy and cookies policy our position regarding certain privacy matters, the type of information we may gather during your visit to the website, how we use and share your information, how you can manage your information and the use of cookies on this Website.

By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy please do not use the Website.

This website is the property of www.3news.com. 

**Information we may collect from you**

1\.       In operating our Website we may collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Website: personally identifiable information (PII) and non-personally identifiable information (non-PII) Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is any information that can individually identify you includes, among other things, information that you may supply to us when you visit the Website, e.g. your company name, your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. Non –personally identifiable information includes information that does not identify you personally, but it may include tracking and usage of information about your location, demographics, use of the Website and the internet. 

We will also process the following data about you:

1.1       Details of your visits to our Website and the resources that you access including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblog statistics and other communication data.

1.2       Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website, such as when you register to receive take part in our reality shows such as subscription of newsletters etc or contact us via the contact us page.

1.3       Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

 **2.         Use of cookies**

Like many websites, we use “cookies”, which are a small text files stored on your computer or equipment when you visit our Website. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. 

This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to monitor traffic, improve our Website and the service that we provide to you.

We may gather information about your computer for our services, your general Internet use, and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our Website to our advertisers.

Such information will not identify you personally; it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. 

This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. It is used by us to analyse how visitors interact with the Website so that we can continue to develop and improve this Website.

All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular areas of our Website.

Any advertising featured on this Website may also incorporate cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our Website.

For more information on cookies you can read the guidance at All About Cookies.

 **3.         Use of your information**

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

3.1       To provide you with information requested from us relating to our products or services and to provide information on third party products and services which we feel may be of interest to you if you have consented to receive such information.

3.2       To meet our contractual commitments to you.

3.3       To notify you about any changes to our Website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.

3.4       If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

3.5       We may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you. We or they may contact you about these goods and services by any of the methods that you consented to at the time your information was collected.

3.6       If you are a new customer, we will only contact you or allow third parties to contact you only when you have provided consent and only by those means you provided consent for.

3.7      If you do not want us to use your data for ourselves or third parties you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent to this when you provide your details to us on the form on which we collect your data.

3.8       Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors such as your area of residence or age group.

3.9 To optimize or improve our products, services and operations.

3.10 To detect investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.

We may also use and/or combine information that we collect off-line, or that we collect or receive from third party sources, to enhance, expand and check the accuracy of user records

 **4.         Storing your personal data**

4.1       We may transfer the data that we collect from you to other locations for processing and storing. In addition, it may be processed by people who work for us or for one of our suppliers. 

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all reasonable steps to make sure that your data is treated securely and in agreement with this privacy policy.

4.2       All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into via our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.

4.3       Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and the transmission of such data is entirely at your own risk.  Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain areas of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

 **5.         Disclosing your information**

5.1       Where applicable, we may disclose some or all the data we collect from you when you visit our site to third parties.

5.2 We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries.

5.2       We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

5.2.1   In the event we sell or by any business assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective buyer or seller of such  business and/or  assets. .

5.2.2    Where we are legally required to disclose your information.

5.2.3    To assist fraud protection and minimize credit risk.

 **6.         Third party links**

You might find from time to time links to third party websites on our Website. These websites may have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies or for any personal data that may be collected through these websites as we have no control over them. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

 **7.          Your Rights**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [address] or [email address] 

**8.         Access to information**

The Data Protection Act 2012, Act 843 gives you the right to access the information that we hold about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with that Act.

Please note that any demand for access may be subject to payment of a fee which covers our costs in providing you with the information requested. Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us using the contact details below.

 **9.         Changes to privacy policy**

Any changes We may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and where appropriate, notified to you. The new terms may be displayed on-screen and you may be required to read and accept them to continue your use of the Website.

 **10.         Contacting us**

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this policy please do not hesitate to contact us at this email: info@3news.com

If you would prefer to write to us then our contact address is  MG Digital Ltd P.O. Box1464, Accra
